Я помню как открыл глаза
I remember how I opened my eyes
И встретил в них тебя
And found you in them
Как первый луч, как тихий звон
Like the first ray of light, like a quiet chime
Как первая гроза
Like the first thunderstorm
Ты словно в небесах заря,
You are like the dawn in the heavens
Ты полная Луна
You are the full Moon
Я помню лишь твои глаза,
I remember only your eyes
А дальше пустота
And after that, emptiness
Сотни ночных дорог напомнят мне тебя
Hundreds of night roads will remind me of you
Я в них терял свою любовь, и заново встречал
On them I lost my love, and found it again
Лишь дай мне посмотреть в последний раз в твои глаза
Just let me look into your eyes for the last time
Я потерял дорогу к ним, я потерял себя
I lost the way to them, I lost myself
И стук колёс как эшафот
And the clatter of wheels, like a scaffold
Уносит тебя в даль
Carries you into the distance
Я выберусь, моя любовь
I will get out, my love
Тебе я в след кричал
I cried out after you
Я научусь тебя любить,
I will learn to love you
Мне без тебя не жить
I cannot live without you
Твой голос мой ориентир,
Your voice is my guide
Я сам себя казнил
I was the one who executed myself
Сотни ночных дорог напомнят мне тебя
Hundreds of night roads will remind me of you
Я в них терял свою любовь, и заново встречал
On them I lost my love, and found it again
Лишь дай мне посмотреть в последний раз в твои глаза
Just let me look into your eyes for the last time
Я потерял дорогу к ним, я потерял себя
I lost the way to them, I lost myself
Лишь дай мне посмотреть в последний раз в твои глаза
Just let me look into your eyes for the last time
Я солнцем обернусь и в них останусь навсегда
I will turn into the sun and stay in them forever